1 - egyptoon  | The 3 Pillars, doing Fundamental Analysis (Roger Federer on your side), things economic central banks politics etc happining, The Key Investment Philosophy of Fundamental Analysis: 1. Economic funds  2. Central Bank Policies & Reactions  3. Effects on FX
2 - how much to risk from your Account size from 2% and below and using SL not lot sizes
3 - position sizing  | knowing your SL, Lot size, 


in the stock market you will need to do this Analysis around 5 thousand times because there are 5 thousand companies in US while 8 times in FOREX because there are 8 currencies to trade


Order Types:


what i understood from the Positioning video is that, after doing the analysis, you will findout that you will be pushed to a certain SL, However, your Risk shouldn't exceed 200$ no matter where the SL. and this is where trading in currency is better than the others. here your SL in the same range of the SL is your Profit as well in the same range and that is why your SL in the opposite size is your SP


so:

and it is going to tell how much you loss in every pip 

so it is like determining your pips price


intill now i understood that after the image of egyptoon the thing is how much you gain/loss for every pip ?
and this is determined by step two which is position sizing

as i said above, the SL is always making other currancy better than the other because my risk is fixed in range not above to 2% and here the SL is the one mostly playing and both SL and my risk determine how much is 1 pip